♪The night wind shakes off
the withered leaves♪
♪I open the window and gaze at the moon♪
♪Haze spreads across the river,
lanterns drifting♪
♪I hear the memories rustling♪
♪Garden flowers shed petals one by one♪
♪Candlelight flickers,
swaying with melancholy♪
♪I sigh by the lamp over the long night♪
♪Past memories unfold scene by scene♪
♪It's all your face♪
♪Boldly trampling over my heart♪
♪Two measures of ink I take,
one for love miswritten♪
♪And another for youth passed♪
♪With endless sorrow,
I once traced your silhouette♪
♪Two measures of ink I take,
one for joy and sorrow♪
♪And another for parting and reunion♪
♪I write until splendor fades,
and I am no more♪
=Prelude of the White Snake=
=Episode 5=
Look at you.
Bullying someone on your own turf,
that's all you've got?
You're from Jinshan Temple?
I am a lay disciple of Jinshan Temple,
and the most handsome one at that.
Right?
Brother...
Who's your brother?
Fine, sister?
What are you looking at?
You're that into Jinshan disciples
at your age?
Too bad,
I'm only into girls like her now.
Get lost!
I just saved you!
Cut the crap.
Where's Rakshasa Bird?
I guess she ran off
after seeing how powerful I am.
Miss Bai,
are you alright?
Miss Bai, what's wrong?
Miss Bai, it's over now.
Don't be afraid.
It was just an illusion.
Young Master Xu,
I saw you in the illusion.
You saw me?
I saw you taking a master.
I also saw
that you avoided your aunt
so you wouldn't burden her.
Then a swarm of snakes surrounded you.
Suddenly, a snake lunged at you.
Just as I tried to protect you,
you accidentally stabbed me
with a dagger.
Then I woke up.
That really was my illusion.
I'm sorry for dragging you into it.
No.
You didn't drag me into it.
It means we are destined to meet.
You're overthinking it.
Aren't we?
No.
Hey, are we?
We definitely are.
We're not.
Miss Bai,
your attendant, Qing,
is still stuck in there.
Right, what should I do?
(Wait, I should be worrying
about the bird instead.)
Don't worry, Young Master Xu.
He can handle it.
He's really fine.
Let's go back.
Yin-Void Illusion reflects
a person's deepest fears and desires.
It either attacks their mind
or numbs their will.
He's not a demon hunter,
so escape won't be easy.
Oh, right.
Young Master Xu, what should we do then?
Don't worry, leave it to me.
(His skills might be weak,)
(but he's quite considerate.)
Do you know how to escape?
That old hag killed
many of my fellow disciples.
I've been hunting her for a long time.
I noticed she hates
seeing people get affectionate.
Come on, lady,
let me show you how to escape.
What a hard slap!
What a cheap trick!
It's a brilliant move, okay?
You're a guy right now.
As the head lay disciple
of Jinshan Temple,
I'm sacrificing my dignity here.
What's with the coyness?
Just for show.
You like kissing, huh?
Then I call the shots.
Look out!
Leifeng Pagoda?
Since you have such a treasure,
why not bring it earlier?
Don't tell me
you don't know how to use it.
I'm just a bit rusty.
Oh no, the spell went wrong!
Don't come any closer!
We're doomed! We're doomed!
Didn't mean to pry into your privacy,
but...
I respect it.
What are you respecting?
Qing, what happened?
Ruined! Everything is ruined!
What's ruined? Aren't you fine?
You little...
Shut up!
Get back here.
What are you grunting at?
Say what you want to say.
You told me not to speak!
What's going on?
This stupid pagoda
(never works when it should.)
(It just malfunctioned.)
(I told you not to come over,
but you wouldn't listen.)
(You took over my array.)
We've formed a bond.
In other words, I'm now your...
Stop talking!
Qing, did you...
Impossible.
Come here.
Go back.
Squat down.
Reach out your left hand.
Wag your tail.
So well-behaved?
What a nice surprise!
What a tragedy!
Don't reveal our identities to anyone.
Rise.
Did I see that right?
That was my temple's
Demon-Subduing Incantation!
When I was slaying demons
three years ago,
I saw your disciples use it.
I am Fahai,
a lay disciple of Jinshan Temple.
May I have your name, brother?
I am Xu Xian, a demon hunter.
Demon hunter?
Well said, well said.
Interesting, very interesting.
What's so interesting?
I think we can
interrogate this demon now.
Why did you massacre Shanyao Village?
And what is your connection
to the white snake demon?
Shanyao Village?
That run-down village on the outskirts?
What's it to me?
And who's white snake demon?
You can play tough,
but I have countless ways
to make you talk.
Just you?
Threats won't work.
Even if you kill me,
I won't admit to things I didn't do.
I only kill Jinshan disciples.
They deserve to die!
The villagers of Shanyao were deceived
into feeding themselves
to an evil demon.
I checked the Demon Codex,
only your kind does this.
The demonic energy on this talisman
points to you as well.
If not you, then who?
Your siblings?
Our Rakshasa Bird clan
has no such sacrificial arts.
Alright, we eat human eyeballs,
but what use do we have
for human sacrifices?
Can we eat them?
You wicked demon,
you keep barking about Jinshan Temple.
What did Jinshan Temple do
for you to spout such nonsense?
A Jinshan disciple toyed with my sister
and slaughtered our clan
on their wedding day.
How do you not deserve to die?
But everyone at Jinshan Temple
is a monk.
How could anyone marry her?
Exactly. If you're going to lie,
make it believable.
Don't believe me?
Go ahead and use the Truth Spell on me
to see if I'm lying!
(The Rakshasa Bird clan hasn't had
such a grand celebration in ages.)
(I heard the groom isn't a demon.)
(What kind of big shot is he?)
Although I don't really like him,
seeing you so happy,
I wish you eternal love.
Thank you, little sis.
Go fetch my golden hairpin.
Sister, you already look stunning today.
Changming?
Changming, why did you kill her?
Heavenly righteousness,
slay all evil demons!
Why rush to kill her?
Are you also involved in this?
I am Changming, a disciple training
at the foot of Jinshan Temple.
She carries the blood
of seven Jinshan Temple disciples.
Why shouldn't I kill her?
As for you two,
as men of righteousness,
you're consorting with a murderous demon
and letting her spout lies
to slander Jinshan Temple!
Fahai, do you still not see your error?
Even if she's a demon,
what she said made sense.
Something is suspicious.
No need to silence her.
Exactly!
You killed her
without getting any answers.
Then how will Jinshan Temple
ever clear its name?
Fine, keep believing a demon's words!
Do you really think Jinshan Temple
wronged the Rakshasa Bird clan first?
Of course we don't think that.
Then what do you think, Fahai?
As the head disciple of Jinshan Temple,
your mind is corrupted by demons.
No wonder you haven't mastered
the Leifeng Pagoda in ten years,
nor have you been ordained!
Farewell.
♪I also gave my youth to someone♪
♪I must admit, you made the journey♪
♪When loving you
became instinct, what's left♪
♪Seals a fate too brutal to amend♪
♪Clumsy and new, we gave our first kiss♪
♪Never thought passionate eyes
would turn cold♪
♪I thought of pulling away,
but I'd barely begun♪
♪Having loved you so deep,
how could I love another♪
♪Even if we're strangers again,
why deny we loved♪
♪Though I'm stubborn,
I never stopped you from loving others♪
♪I shouldn't have been so foolish
to think there was still hope♪
♪But you won't even admit what we had♪
♪Even if we're strangers again,
why deny we loved♪
♪Though I have questions,
I never questioned you♪
♪I'll lock you away and set myself free♪
♪After all, I'm the one you deny♪
♪Having ever loved♪